(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-08T22:19:43.638997",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Hello!
Hey everyone!
Yeah, over here!
It's me!
It's 3D Biboo!
Yay! Wow!
What?
What's wrong?
It's me, Biboo, the moai.
Yeah, the big moai in front of you, that's me!
3D Biboo, ain't it great?
Ain't it beautiful?
Yeah.
What?
Is this not the Biboo you wanted to see?
Maybe if you say please, I'll come out.
Come on.
Okay, there we go!
Kira kira Koseki!
溶けないシュガー 甘いマジック
Tokenai sugar, amai majikku
ふわりたゆたう 時間 (知らない)
Fuwari tayutau jikan (shiranai)
迷路 (Weaver) 見つけて?
Meiro (Weaver) Mitsukete?
溶けない sugar
Sugar that won't ever melt
甘い magic
sweet magic,
ふわり 漂う 時間
floating softly through time.
知らない flavor 見つけたら
If I find a flavor I don't know,
世界中が きらめく new world
the whole world sparkles, a new world!
始まりは ドキドキして
It starts with a pounding heart,
めぐりめぐり 物語
a revolving, turning story.
幸せを 集めて
Gathering up happiness,
夢の 旅をしよう
let's go on a journey of dreams!
わん、とぅー、せーの！
One, two, ready, go!
願うの
I'm wishing,
ねえ 幾千億の 奇跡
hey, billions of miracles...
届けたい この ときめき
I want to reach you with this heartbeat,
永遠 紡ぐ 光
light weaving on for eternity,
プリズムの 魔法 みたい
just like the prism's magic.
誰だって 寂しい
Anyone gets lonely,
そんな 夜には 見上げた 空に 無数の 宝石
on nights like that, looking up at a sky full of countless gems.
なんだって できる
Anything is possible
照らし合う なら 眩しい ほどに きらめく new world
if we shine together, a dazzlingly sparkling new world!
今 以上に わくわくして
Even more excited than before,
ぐるりまわる 影模様
shadows dancing all around us.
揺蕩う 波 ゆられ
Swaying with the drifting waves,
ひとやすみしよう
let's take a little rest.
おやすみ
Good night...
目が 覚めたら
When I wake up,
ほんの 少し 広がる 虹
a rainbow spreads out just a little bit.
モノクロに 色が 咲く
Colors bloom in the monochrome world.
わん、とぅー、せーの！
One, two, ready, go!
願うの
I'm wishing,
ねえ 幾千億の 奇跡
hey, billions of miracles...
届けたい この ときめき
I want to reach you with this heartbeat,
永遠 紡ぐ 光
light weaving on for eternity,
プリズムの 魔法 みたい
just like the prism's magic.
輝きと あの 未来
Brilliance and that future,
プリズムの 魔法を キミに
the prism's magic to you!
Yay! Hello everyone!
Bombiju! Yay!
No, stop! You're embarrassing me, feet! Stop that! Not on 3D! Oh, Biboo...
No!
Dang it! Stop! Okay, okay, we're good.
Bombiju! I'm Koseki Bijou, sparkling gem of Hololive English Advent, and today...
Biboo's in 3D, yay!
Well, before we get to business...
Hashtag! #hashtag, #biboo3D!
Please post any cute pictures or any reactions to my cute 3D body, okay?
Yeah!
Ta-da! I'm in full power now!
Hehe, nothing can limit me!
You've been waiting a long time, huh? Huh? For me to make these cute poses, to make these cute wiggles... Look at my body! Okay, fine, feet.
That's what you wanted, right?
This? Yeah. Well, there you go.
Okay, well, what do you think?
Do you like my place?
I actually left this place before I went to prison, so it looks a little different.
Yeah, it looks a little different now.
I guess no one took care of it while I was gone, but isn't it pretty?
Look at all these crystals, I made those!
I made those, by the way. I made that one, and that one, and that one, and that one, and that one! Yeah!
So here, take a look...
Ooh, there's some green over there, there's a giant hole there, and there, and there... but that's okay, there's a tree, look at that tree! Cute! Isn't it pretty?
I like it so much
Pebbles
Thank you for coming today
I'm so excited to share with you everything
I have in store
but the first thing I sang
Did you recognize it?
Obviously you did
because that was my first original song!
Prism in My Hold
or Prism Magic
Did you like it?
I'm really proud of it and I hope it made you feel happy
and magical. And yeah!
Thank you so much for listening
and I'm so excited to show you the rest of the 3D showcase.
Yay!
What's that?
Stairs?
Woah, where is that goal?
It looks pretty deep.
And uh what's that?
God!
Help!
Get me out of here!
Dang it.
Ow... my head...
Ow, what was that?
Oh...
Huh?
Where?
Am I?
It's so dark in here.
Hello?
What's this? A crystal?
Oh, it's so shiny.
What is this for?
It looks magical.
Huh?
Oh...
Oh, what is this?
Uh-oh.
I feel like this is something I'm quite familiar with.
Do I walk through it?
I feel like I have to walk through it.
Hmm...
I bet there's something behind that door.
Let's go find out!
Woah, let's go!
Woah, this place is big.
I wonder what it's for?
Eh?
Why am I holding a staff?
A weapon?
I have bad feelings about this.
Eh?
Why do I hear boss music?
Don't tell me I have to fight that thing.
I guess I should, okay.
You got this, Biboo.
You've done this before, it's just more physical now.
Come at me, bro.
Okay, watch this.
Pebbles, go! Yeah!
Okay, I just have to duck.
Okay. Okay.
Yeah, I'm not scared of you.
Okay, maybe a little bit. Okay!
Take that! Yeah!
You're too slow.
Try and get me.
Boom!
More, more, more, more!
Yeah! You're too slow!
Okay, take that!
Take that!
Oh, he's stuck! He's stuck!
Okay, I think I'm running low on mana.
Thirsty?
Ah! Ah, got it!
Okay, I'm ready for you.
I'm recharged.
Here we go, pebbles!
Ha-ha!
Yeah!
Ha!
Take this!
Why isn't this working?
I'm not doing that much damage.
Eh?
Ah! No!
Kyaa!
Ahhh!
No, I'm going to...
Oh man, I'm dead!
I died.
I don't know why,
the pebbles... they didn't do that much damage.
Maybe I have to think of something else.
Let me see...
Let me see if I have anything...
Oh, yeah!
I see, let's use this.
Okay, I'm ready now.
Round two, here we go!
Yeah!
Okay, big boss man thing, whatever you are, I'm back, and I got a big weapon this time.
I'm not afraid of you.
Here we go!
Ha!
Boom!
Oh, did that hurt? Did that hurt?
Ha!
You're too slow.
I'm faster than you.
And then take that!
My health's low.
Body? Okay.
Okay, I feel better.
Are you dying yet?
Please die!
Oh, you go away!
Wait, why isn't it doing anything?
Okay?
Ah! No!
Dang it!
I thought switching builds would work.
Thank you, respawn crystal, I appreciate it.
What should I do now?
I got to fight that boss.
Oh, I have an idea.
Okay, I'm going to dual wield this time, that's going to work.
Yeah!
And I'm going to summon my crystals too.
Ha! Yeah!
Okay, I'm ready.
One more try, I'm going to beat that boss. Let's go!
Yeah!
Curses, you big boss man thing,
I hereby vow,
you will rule this day. It is I!
Koseki Biboo, your fears made rock!
Oh! Oh! Oh! Oh!
Wait!
Ahhhhh!
I get stunned!
I understand!
Let me... Ouch! Ouch!
No!
Oh, come on!
Oh, dear!
Hah! Stop block!
What? Go!
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
Ouch! Stop that! No!
Oh! Take that!
Hah!
No!
Ah!
Go away!
Hah! Hah!
Hah!
Yeah, you like that, huh?
Get tired? Oh, well, well, well, he's mad. Oh, dear.
Ahhhhh!
Oh, I get it! I get it!
Come here! Hey, you!
Over here! Over here! I'm over here! Hey, hey! Hey!
Ugh!
Hah!
Take that!
Yeah!
Okay!
Ready? Hah! Ha!
Hah! Ha! Hah!
Ha! Ha!
Hah!
Yeah! I won! Let's go!
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!
Eh? Ah!
So finally you're here, you finally defeated the first boss.
Kaela!
What are you doing here?
Too bad for you, I am the real final boss.
Uh-oh.
Yeah, so if you want to win, you need to defeat me.
Really? Yeah!
Come at me, bro.
Really?
Yeah! Hmm.
Wait! Why do you have three health bars?
Yeah, why the...
Ah, I'm tired, whatever.
Oh, you're tired? Okay then.
Ahhhhh!
Blech!
眠れない夜には ひとりでため息
On sleepless nights, I sigh all by myself.
みんなはどうなの? なんだか寂しい
How is everyone else doing? Somehow, I feel lonely.
らしくないなんてね 笑うのはやめて
Don't just laugh and say it's unlike me.
ホントの私を 知らないだけだよ
You just don't know the real me.
広い大地に 一粒の種 根っこを伸ばして
A single seed in the vast earth, growing its roots,
まだ青い 実をつけた オレンジ色に
bearing still-green fruit, wanting to quickly become
早く なりたい果実 キミの光を浴びて
an orange fruit, bathing in your light.
理想や夢は膨らむばかり 気づいてよ ねぇ
Ideals and dreams just keep swelling, please notice me.
オレンジ 今日も 食べてみたけど
Orange, I tried eating one again today,
まだすっぱくて 泣いた
but it was still so sour I cried.
私みたいで残せないから ぜんぶ食べた
Because it's just like me and I can't leave any, I ate it all.
好きだよ 泣けるよ 好きだよ 好きだよ
I love it, I can cry, I love it, I love it.
似てても違うよ マンダリン オレンジ
Even if they look similar, they're different: mandarin oranges.
友達 恋人 2人のココロも 傷つけたくない
Friends or lovers, I don't want to hurt either of our hearts.
私は逃げてた そうしたら光も 射してはくれない
I was running away; if I do that, even the light won't shine on me.
奇跡なのにね 出会いも恋も
Even though it's a miracle, encounters and love...
1つ2つと 星が出てきた
One by one, the stars came out,
夕焼け あの日の 帰り道で
on that sunset walk home.
傷つき たくない
I didn't want to get hurt,
私は 逃げてた
so I kept running away.
そしたら 光も
But then, even the light
さしては くれない
wouldn't shine down on me.
奇跡なんてさ
Miracles and such—
出会いも恋も
encounters and love—
誰もつぼみも まだ
buds and all, none of it yet.
青い 未練さえも
Even my blue regrets...
オレンジ色の あの日みたいな夕焼けは 思い出ささせてくれる
That sunset like that orange day makes me remember it all.
二つの影が 手を繋いでるみたいがあった
It felt like two shadows holding hands.
オレンジいつか 甘くなるから それとも 痺れちゃうの
Orange, will it sweeten up, or will it make me numb?
私の未来 知りたくなくて 全部食べた
I didn't want to know my future, so I ate it all up!
スパイス
Super spicy—
好きだけど 泣けるよ
I love it, but it makes me cry.
オレンジ色に早くになりたいから 傷つき君の光を浴びて
I want to turn orange quickly, bathed in your light of hurt,
理想の夢は 膨らむばかり 気づいてよね
my ideal dreams just swell up, won't you notice?
オレンジ皮も食べてみたけど まだ 酸っぱくてないの
I tried eating the orange peel too, but it's still not sour—
私にタイレン 残さないから 全部食べた
leaving no trace in me, I ate it all up!
好きだよ 泣けるよ
I love it, it makes me cry.
好きだよ 好きだよ 好きだよ
I love it, I love it, I love it!
スパイス 泣けるよ 好きだよ
Super, it makes me cry, I love it!
好きだよ
I love it!
Thanks for singing with me, even though you bounced me and dragged me here, dang it!
How— how do you respond from that? I thought you were gonna just die and then the treaty was gonna be over!
How do you respond from that? I thought you were gonna just die and the treaty was over!
I have a treaty! This is mine, Kyla! And you almost ruined it by killing me, no!
I have a treaty! This is mine, Kyla! And you almost ruined it by killing me!
I'm gonna get my revenge someday!
Really? Yeah, I'll beat you so-- I gotta wait for that, yeah.
Really? Yeah, I'll beat you so— I gotta wait for that, yeah.
Yeah, and you will hear the last of me.
I mean, you you invited me here, right? To sing?
I mean, you invited me here, right? To sing?
To sing, not to bonk me! I invite you to sing together!
To sing, not to bonk me! I invited you to sing together!
And you came in and I was already being the boss, and then I was... dang it!
That's the bonk twist, right? I'm the final boss!
Why do you have three life bars with the Biboo? You're too weak!
You're too weak! I'm gonna get stronger and beat you!
I'm gonna wait for you, but it was fun, you know? Singing with you, it was fun.
I guess it was fun. I guess we were pretty cute, right?
No, you cute, I'm cool.
No, I think we were both pretty cute, right?
Look at that, look at how we look together. Where's my hammer? Can I have my hammer again?
Look at our... Where's my hammer? Can I have my hammer again?
Yeah, we're cuties. You have to have both! Haha. How cool!
Yeah, we're cuties. You have to have both! How cool!
I mean, you can be both, right? No.
No, you cute, I'm cool. No.
I can be cool too, look. Look at that, with that smile? No, it's not working.
Oh, well. I'll work on it.
Do you like my place? Yeah! Oh, this is your place?
Yeah, it's my place. I really love that. Can I— can I mine that?
No, it's my... my decorations!
I'm gonna mine that later after this, whenever you're not saying... I'm gonna mine that! You know what, you can leave now.
Oh, really? Yeah! Oh, really? You brought nothing but trouble here.
Oh, just like that? I see how it is. Well, if you say no, you can stay.
No, I'm getting my exit. What? What are you doing?
Oh! Wait! Kyla!
Bye! Oh, I guess he's gone. Aw, well, thank you, Kyla, for singing with me!
Bye! Oh, I guess she's gone. Aw, well, thank you, Kyla, for singing with me!
Grindstone together forever!
Yeah.
But now that I've been rudely put here by Kayla,
I guess we should explore the place a little bit, huh?
Want to go?
Let's go.
Okay.
Yay!
The air feels good over here.
Whoa!
This place looks a lot different from when I last left it,
but I kind of like it better this way. Yeah.
Oh, there's a Moai! Look!
Oh, nice Moai. I approve.
I approve. Very nice, very tall, very cuckoldy, yes.
Oh, look. Grass.
What's this?
Biboo's touching grass! Oh!
Look, the flowers. Oh, they're so pretty.
Ah, that feels good.
Yeah.
That smells great.
Oh, well, grass isn't so bad. I kind of like it.
Okay, let's keep exploring.
Oh, everything is so pretty.
Oh, is that a chair?
Oh, it looks comfy.
It's not a plastic chair, but it'll do.
I will sit on it, but not now. Later.
Later, we got a lot of exploring to do.
Oh, hey! That's where I was before!
Yeah, until Kayla
brutally bullied, bogs me and dragged me here. Whatever, I didn't have to walk so
brutally bullied, bossed me and dragged me here. Whatever, I didn't have to walk so...
Thanks Kayla, I guess.
Oh, crystals, and look at the architecture, all the sky! Whoa!
Oh, what's that in the tall grass?
Is that a wild Pebblemon? Oh, it's so cute!
Can I have it? I want it. I want it.
I got an idea. Okay.
Hah! Yah!
Hah! Yah! Hah! Yah!
Okay.
Yeah, I'm gonna I'm gonna catch it with this.
Okay, I got one shot, though.
I'm ready. I'm ready.
Highsishiwa! Tonight!
High-speed war! Tonight!
Boom! Yay! Let's go see. Let's go see.
I caught a Pebblemon!
I caught a Pebblemon! Yay!
I caught a Pebblemon! I caught a Pebblemon! Yay, yeah, yeah!
Nice weather.
I hate it.
Why are we here? I don't know.
Hey! Oh, hey!
Hi.
Our eyes met! We have to battle.
Why? Fight me, bro!
Wait, fight you?
What? Did Towa-sama, Mama say bro? What?
Ah!
Come on! Senpai tax, baby.
Wait, but there's you and there's little me.
I need help! Is anybody here?
Here we go!
You're here!
We will defeat them!
Yeah!
I don't think so!
I'm not scared of you!
No way, yeah, good luck, Kohaa!
It's time to pebble!
Team, baby, ready to fight!
Biboo, that's right.
Go Pebble Monster!
That was so peeking, we can't hold back.
Okay, that was kind of weird.
It's my turn now!
Here's bloody nightmare!
Oh, oh! Oh, oh! Oh, oh!
That's okay, it's okay, it's okay! Don't cry.
What's there?
I will teach you how it's done.
Babon! From the fiery depths, yes, eternal embers of flames!
Wait, wait! Oh, no hits!
It's my turn! Okay, morimon, use bloody nightmare!
Uh, okay. Wow.
Okay, little buddy, you can do it.
Nice! Come on!
You can do it!
Who's next?
Okay, my turn! Go survive!
Oh, no!
That was weird. Okay, let's get.
Nice shot! Nice shot!
Diamond wall! Eh? What are you doing?
That was a weird battle.
Okay, I want to do a cool move too.
Come on, Kosaki Bijou, I'll show you.
No! Judgment!
Ray and go!
Gosh! Oh! Okay, so cute! Oh, Yoshi! Yoshi!
I think we're winning!
This battle is... You know what?
Just stay there.
What? Huh? What?
Betray Bijou? Oh, what a great idea! I love that!
Yeah, all right, Bijou, time to pay the step by step.
What you're going to do?
What you're going to do? What you're going to do, Biboo?
It's you! Help me! Attempt ten anime betrayals! Help, I need help! Get them! Get them! Get them!
You winners, that thing I've never seen that thing in my life.
What is that? What is that?
What is going on?
Halkity!
What?
Wait a minute! Look up!
Biboo is the winner!
I won! I want, I want, I want, I want.
And now you guys have to sing a song with me.
Yeah!
Biboo, I don't know if I can sing.
I won! I won! I won! I won! I won!
Yeah! Guys, what's that? What's that?
That thing? What's that?
Knock up!
INSIDE IDENTITY 居場所はどこ？
INSIDE IDENTITY, where do I belong?
勘違いが恥ずかとか 素直さが痛いとか
Misconceptions are embarrassing, and honesty is painful.
誰かなんと言おうと 正しさなんてわかんないぜ
No matter what anyone says, I don't know what's right.
普通に流れていく日常に 無理して馴染ませた
I tried to fit into the ordinary flow of everyday life.
沈みすぎた個性をたちを 噛んで飲んで吐いて笑う
I chewed up, swallowed, spat out, and laughed at my sunken individuality.
こんな僕をわかってほしい
I want you to understand this me.
言いたいけど言えなくって
I want to say it, but I can't.
なんで誰もわかってくんないのと
Why doesn't anyone understand?
思うのは贅沢なのかな？なのかなぁ？
Is it too much to ask? Is it?
感情的な太陽は熱を上げすぎてどうにかなりそう
The emotional sun raises the heat too high and I'm about to lose it.
叫びたくてしょうがない がむしゃらに求めてるidentity ああ
I want to scream, I'm desperately seeking my identity!
(inside my feeling inside my justice 邪魔しないで居場所はどこ？)
(Inside my feeling, inside my justice, don't bother me, where do I belong?)
「可愛い〜」って誰かが言ってとなりにこだまして
"So cute," someone said, echoing around.
頭に『？』浮かべ 寝て起きても今日も快晴
With a "?" floating in my head, I sleep, wake up, and it's sunny again today.
飾ったデコレーションが苦手な僕がいるよ
I'm the kind of person who struggles with fancy decorations.
僕にしかできないことがあるってのも知ってんだけど
I know I have things only I can do, but I wonder...
どう見られてるかが心配なのは？
Are you worried about how you're perceived?
居場所はどこ？
Where do I belong?
勘違いが恥ずかしいこととか
Misunderstandings being embarrassing,
素直さが痛いとか
or honesty being painful—
誰が何と言おうと
no matter what anyone says,
正しさなんてわからないぜ
I still don't know what's right.
普通に流れていく日常に
To the ordinary days flowing by,
無理して馴染ませた
I forced myself to fit in.
沈んでしまった個性たちを
All of my submerged personalities
噛んで飲んで吐いて笑う
I chew and swallow, spit out, and laugh.
inside my feeling
inside my justice
inside my justice—
邪魔しないで 居場所はどこ？
don't interfere, where do I belong?
「可愛いさ」って誰かが言って
Someone says, "You're so cute,"
となりでこだまして
and it echoes around me.
頭に「？」浮かべ
A "?" pops up in my head.
寝て起きて今日も快晴
I sleep and wake up, and it's sunny today too.
飾ったデコレーションが
The decorations I put up
苦手な僕がいるよ
are something I struggle with.
僕にしかできないことがあるってのも
Though I know there is something only I can do,
知ってんだけれど
I still wonder...
どう見られているかが心配なの？
Is how I'm seen that worrying?
頷くことは正しいの？
Is nodding the right thing to do?
「本当はどうなのか」が気になるよ
"What is the truth?" bothers me.
答えを探すの
I want to find the answer,
見つけたい 見つけたい
I want to find it, find it.
孤独を知って 愛を知る
Knowing loneliness, knowing love—
割り切れるほど 大人じゃないんだが
not mature enough to cleanly divide them, but
寂しいけれど 譲れない
though it's lonely, I won't give it up.
僕だけのブレない identity ああ
My unbreakable identity, ah!
生き残るだけじゃ駄目さ
Just surviving is not enough.
何かを残したいからここにいるわけさ
I'm here because I want to leave something behind.
誰かに貰った快楽が
The pleasure I received from someone
僕の幸せとは限らないぜ
is not necessarily my own happiness.
名も無い毎日だけど
Every day may be nameless, but
意味を確立できる日は来るよ
the day to establish its meaning will come.
中二病と呼ばれても
Even if called delusional,
モラトリアムの渦の中
in the whirlpool of moratorium...
感情的な太陽は熱を上げすぎてどうかなりそう
The emotional sun is burning way too hot and I'm about cooked in the head
叫びたくてしょうがない
I can't help but want to scream,
がむしゃらに関わる identity ああ
desperately seeking my identity, ah.
(inside my feeling
inside my justice
inside my justice—
邪魔しないで 居場所はどこ？)
don't interfere, where do I belong?)
生き残るだけじゃ駄目さ
Just surviving is not enough,
何かを残したいからここにいるわけさ
I'm here because I want to leave something behind.
誰かに貰った快楽が
The pleasure I received from someone
僕の幸せとは限らないぜ
is not necessarily my own happiness.
名も無い毎日だけど
Every day may be nameless, but
意味を確立できる日は来るよ
the day to establish its meaning will come.
中二病と呼ばれても
Even if called delusional,
モラトリアムの渦の中
in the whirlpool of moratorium...
感情的な太陽は熱を上げすぎてどうかなりそう
The emotional sun is burning way too hot and I'm about cooked in the head,
叫びたくてしょうがない
I can't help but want to scream,
がむしゃらに関わる identity ああ
desperately seeking my identity, ah.
(inside my feeling...)
感情的な太陽は熱を上げすぎてどうかなりそう
The emotional sun is burning way too hot and I'm about cooked in the head,
叫びたくてしょうがない
I can't help but want to scream,
がむしゃらに求めてる identity ああ
desperately seeking my identity, ah.
inside my feeling
inside my justice
inside my justice—
邪魔しないで 居場所はどこ？
don't interfere, where do I belong?
inside my feeling
inside my justice
inside my justice—
邪魔しないで
don't interfere,
居場所はどこ？
where do I belong?
Yay! Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Good job, good job! Yippee! Congratulations!
Congratulations!
We did it! Look at this 3D!
Thanks for inviting us.
Do you have any poses you want me to do?
Do the worm!
Go, go, go! Woo!
Good job!
So Yishuffling!
Thank you for inviting us!
How do you feel?
I feel very good.
I'm so happy I chose this song because, you know, we're all very chuuni, right?
Chuuni? Simp for the chuuni?
No, I just chose Towa-sama because I wanted to sing with Towa-sama.
Towa-sama is so cute!
Yosshu! Yosshu! Chuuniz!
Chuuni? Chuuni? Chuuni? Chuuniz generation, yeah!
Thank you!
Thank you guys so much for being a part of my 3D! I'm so honored!
No problem! But next time I'm gonna meet, I'm gonna beat you in Fall Guys, so you know, so watch out.
You gotta watch out for us though. Got to pay your Senpai tax.
I'll fight back! We're going down with a fight! Yeah, got the core.
Well, we wish you luck for the rest of your 3D!
Biboo! Bye-bye!
Bye! Bye-bye!
Ah, they're gone now.
Oh, that was so much fun singing with my sempai.
Ah, I'm so happy.
But, I guess now it's just us, huh? Mhm.
Wait! Wait a second.
Ah! It's you! Hello!
Everyone! Everyone, I want to introduce you to my buddy.
This is the Grand Executioner of Worlds!
What? That's your name?
Yes, Grand Executioner of Worlds.
Fine, you can call him Geo or whatever, I guess, but his real name's Grand Executioner of World, okay? Geo.
Geo. Cute! Thank you for coming!
Actually, did you know Geo and I have been friends for a long, long time?
But, you know, when I got, you know, in jail, we kind of got separated,
uh, because he Oh, don't be, don't be so sad!
I'm back now! Have you been waiting here for me this whole time?
Ah, thank you, Geo, my loyal companion. I missed you too. Ah.
Well, you're going to be seeing a lot more of Geo from now on, so
Yeah! I'm so happy to finally introduce you to him. Yeah!
So everybody, how is my 3D debut? Did you like it? Did you have fun?
I had so much fun with Kaila, and Tora Sempai, and Kaela, and Hoshimatic Azu.
Yeah, it was such a good time. I had so much fun.
Wait a second. Hmm. Was there something that you wanted me to do in 3D? Like a very specific, I don't know...
dance or something? I think you know what I'm talking about. But, ah, I'm a little tired.
I don't think I have the energy to do her...
Sticking out your gyatt for the rizzler, you're so fanum tax, you're so pibby, I just want to be your rizzler.
You didn't think I would end this 3D without doing that, huh? Get Biboo-taxed!
Yay!
But now, I have some ooh, announcements to make.
Wait, wait, wait, Geo, Geo, Geo, Geo. Do you want to help me? Do you want to help me announce some things?
Okay, cool.
So, my announcement today is... Merch! 3D Live Merch, yay!
And first up, I have...
What are those? I'll tell you what they are. They are Biboo's... candy feet room slippers!
Now you can match with Biboo. Look! Look! Check it out! We can both have candy feet together. Yeah!
Wait, where are you looking? Stop. No, no, don't look. Don't look at that. No. Get the slippers and look at it yourself. Yeah.
Isn't it great? Please make sure you get the slippers and match with Biboo. Yeah.
Well, that's all for merch today. I hope you like those special items.
But now, the very next song is going to be the last one of this 3D debut.
Oh, man. I was having so much fun. Are you sad, Pebbles? Are you sad?
It's okay. This next song is extra special, and I think it's going to be really good and you're going to enjoy it. So, are you ready?
Let's go!
泣いたような声でさ
With a tearful voice,
静かに笑うんだ
I quietly laugh.
想像を映した
A snapshot of my imagination,
彩のパレット
In this colorful palette.
Please, distinguish me.
溢れ出す色を
Overflowing colors,
誰か止めてよ
Someone, please stop them,
消えちゃう
Before I disappear.
「愛してる」を溶かした青は、やさしいなみだ
The blue with "I love you" melted in is a gentle teardrop,
「ありがとう」を浮かべた赤に、やさしいうた
In the red that "Thank you" floated with is a gentle song.
紡ぎ出す群青
Spinning ultramarine,
巡る記憶に
Surrounds my memories,
I will be eraser's mind
絡まった僕らの
Our entwined
未来が色づく
future changes color.
「愛してる」を描いた黒は、やさしいきおく
The black that drew out "I love you" is a tender memory,
「ありがとう」を溢せた白に、やさしいきす
In the white that "Thank you" was spilled is a gentle kiss.
紡ぎ出す群青
Spinning ultramarine,
巡る記憶に
Surrounds my memories,
絡まった僕らの
Our entwined
未来が色づく
future changes color.
Dear Pebbles,
Hi! It's Biboo!
How did you enjoy the showcase?
Did it Rock? (heh)
To be honest, I missed you all lots these past few months!
Not being able to stream as much and hang out with everyone was a little lonely...
BUT! I knew the end result was going to be worth it!
So, Biboo took all the feelings of her Pebbles who were cheering her on and turned it into POWER.
She learned so many new things like how to dance and different ways to sing all in the hopes that Pebbles would be proud of her one day!
I hope one of those days is today.
But TODAY is just the beginning!
getting
After today,
we've unlocked a whole new DIMENSION of Biboo!
We're just getting started!
So, no matter when or where you found me,
I hope you'll continue to join me on this journey,
TOGETHAAA!
This small rock is gonna do BIG things!!
Today, I am shining bright because of you.
From bottom of my heart,
From the bottom of my heart,
Thank you, Pebbles!
Love, Biboo.